[
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4317464986&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with TypeScript?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 3,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T05:33:59.874Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4317464986&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Are you willing to participate in a coding challenge to showcase your skills?Are you willing to participate in a coding challenge to showcase your skills?",
    "answerType": "boolean",
    "answer": true,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T05:33:59.888Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4311471398&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with HL7 Standards?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 0,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T05:54:47.691Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4311471398&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of Hospitals and Health Care experience do you currently have?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 2,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T05:54:47.699Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4311471398&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with React Native?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 0,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T06:22:36.829Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4318531454&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of leadership experience do you have?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 7,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:10:52.495Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4293288933&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with MySQL?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 1,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:42:25.665Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4315741709&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "How many eyars of experience with AWS JavaScript SDK (v3+)?",
    "answerType": "text",
    "answer": 1,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:51:38.806Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4315741709&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Do you have experience building applications from scratch?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:51:38.831Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4315741709&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Do you have hands on experience with Express.js?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:51:38.843Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4305771372&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "What are the last two numerical digits of Edison's lightbulb patent?",
    "answerType": "text",
    "answer": 98,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:53:18.499Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4305771372&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Engineering scrums are at 9am EST each day as most of the team is East Coast based. Will you be able to make this time work each day?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:53:18.524Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4305771372&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Are you willing to take a 30 to 60 minute live engineering coding challenge as part of the interview process?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:53:18.537Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4305771372&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Are you currently using AI tools such as Cursor?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:53:18.547Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "unknown",
    "url": "https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/search/?currentJobId=4318577031&f_AL=true&f_WT=2&geoId=103644278&origin=JOB_SEARCH_PAGE_JOB_FILTER&refresh=true",
    "question": "Do you possess the ability to obtain a security clearance? US Citizenship, clean criminal/credit history is required?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T21:53:41.488Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4323934464",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Azure AI Foundry?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 0,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:01:41.315Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317724670",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Figma (Software)?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 7,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:02:25.113Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317724670",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with REST APIs?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 13,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:02:25.121Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317724670",
    "question": "How many years of experience you have in Figma",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 7,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:02:26.856Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4331143912",
    "question": "What is your expected hourly pay on W2 basis?",
    "answerType": "text",
    "answer": "90",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:03:05.638Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4331143912",
    "question": "Do you need Visa Sponsorship, now or in the future to work on our W2?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-24T22:03:06.243Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4315977297",
    "question": "Have you led or managed a development team before?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T02:32:41.951Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4318164142",
    "question": "What is your desired annual salary range for this role?",
    "answerType": "text",
    "answer": "$166,400-$187,200",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T02:38:51.586Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4318164142",
    "question": "Which country are you based out of?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "United States",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T02:38:51.629Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "United States",
        "value": "United States"
      },
      {
        "text": "Canada",
        "value": "Canada"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ireland",
        "value": "Ireland"
      },
      {
        "text": "United Kingdom",
        "value": "United Kingdom"
      },
      {
        "text": "Australia",
        "value": "Australia"
      },
      {
        "text": "Poland",
        "value": "Poland"
      },
      {
        "text": "Bulgaria",
        "value": "Bulgaria"
      },
      {
        "text": "Czechia",
        "value": "Czechia"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "value": "Ukraine"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hungary",
        "value": "Hungary"
      },
      {
        "text": "Phillippines",
        "value": "Phillippines"
      },
      {
        "text": "I live somewhere other than the options listed above",
        "value": "I live somewhere other than the options listed above"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4292487408",
    "question": "Do you live within 100 miles of the San Francisco Bay Area?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T02:59:49.709Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4331186481",
    "question": "How many years experience do you have writing production level code?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 13,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T03:41:39.143Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4318623432",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Google Cloud Platform (GCP)?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 0,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T03:52:42.624Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4315060233",
    "question": "Do you have 5+ years of full-stack experience building modern, scalable web applications?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:14:14.875Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4315060233",
    "question": "Have you built production-level applications using AWS Lambda or DynamoDB?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:14:14.893Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4315060233",
    "question": "Are you available to work overlapping hours with U.S. Pacific Time?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:14:14.903Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317101155",
    "question": "Have you integrated front-end web experiences using Webflow?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:15:33.745Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317101155",
    "question": "Have you worked in a small startup or early-stage team (<20 people)?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:15:33.762Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317960332",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with Salesforce.com?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 0,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:16:11.461Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317960332",
    "question": "How many years of work experience do you have with GraphQL?",
    "answerType": "number",
    "answer": 1,
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:16:11.471Z"
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4305771372",
    "question": "Do you currently reside in Eastern or Central time zones?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:35:44.117Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "jobId": "4317464986",
    "question": "Are you willing to participate in a coding challenge to showcase your skills?",
    "answerType": "dropdown",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-25T04:36:54.842Z",
    "options": [
      {
        "text": "Select an option",
        "value": "Select an option"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yes",
        "value": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "text": "No",
        "value": "No"
      }
    ]
  }
]